<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on Pavan Kemparaju</title>
    <link>/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on Pavan Kemparaju</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 15:19:08 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Hackathons</title>
      <link>/blog/hackathons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Apr 2018 20:33:28 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/hackathons/</guid>
      <description>I was at UW-Madison&amp;rsquo;s Madhacks Mini today. This was a 12 hour, beginner-friendly mini-hackathon to give new hackers a glimpse into what hackathons are like.
So why hack? What are the chances that I will wake up at 8 AM on a Saturday, wolf down whatever breakfast I can get my hands on and get down to brainstorming, coding and trying out new things? Practically nothing.
Stashed across Keep and One Note and Wunderlist are ideas of things I wanted to build, ideas that seem really cool but are relegated to being looked at longingly every other week - &amp;ldquo;If only I had time&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why Write</title>
      <link>/blog/why_write/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Apr 2018 22:58:00 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/why_write/</guid>
      <description>Why create a blog at all and why write about random things? Things people may not care about or find &amp;lsquo;useful&amp;rsquo;.
George Orwell said that there are 4 reasons to write:
 Sheer egoism- The desire to seem clever, to be talked about, to be remembered after death, to get your own back on grown-ups who snubbed you in childhood, etc. Aesthetic enthusiasm- The desire to create something beautiful. Having &amp;ldquo;pleasure in the impact of one sound on another, in the firmness of good prose or the rhythm of a good story.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Go (Hu)go</title>
      <link>/blog/gohugo/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Mar 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/gohugo/</guid>
      <description>This site was built using the Hugo static site generator. https://gohugo.io/ and the Future Imperfect theme
I found the Giraffe Academy Youtube tutorial about hugo very helpful in understanding how hugo works. Link for the interested: Giraffe Academy Hugo - Static Site Generator | Tutorial
The site is hosted on my github repo pavankm/pavankm.github.io
I purchased the domain name from Namecheap using the github student pack.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>